Very...
Yes, Poe! I wrote Poe!
Ha!
Huh!
What's this?
It's done!
I'm satisfied!
Hello everyone!
My name is Kaho Kobayashi, attendance number 11 at ABC private preparatory school!
So, last time...
I painted the walls completely white.
It became a big canvas!
So this time
I would like to do some coloring, coloring time!
High ratings, channel subscriptions, likes! and comments, etc.
I hope you enjoy it!
Today, I'd like to introduce you to
I'd like to invite Mr. Kodaira, who is a teacher of paint.
Mr. Kodaira, who is a paint master
Mr. Kodaira, who is a paint teacher, and we will paint together!
Mr. Kodaira!
Please help us!
Please help me!
This is my first time to paint on a wall.
What should I do first?
I'd like to start by rubbing the areas I don't want to stain!
Yes, sure!
Yes, from the left.
From the left...
I'm not very good at sticking straight...
It's not pretty at all.
No problem!
Thank you!
It's fine!
It's not a booger, it's a snowflake.
Actually, you love it?
Ha! Quick! Quick!
Early and beautiful is the best, right?
You're late.
I said it backwards.
Put the vinyl over this in the same way.
Here you go.
This is great.
It's got vinyl on it.
From the top.
This is on top of the masking tape that you just put on.
You just put it on.
Why is that?
It's okay to just use the tape with the vinyl on it.
but if you put masking tape under it
I think it's better to put masking tape under it.
I think it's better to put it on.
I see.
I'm in!
Great, only a paint shop can touch it.
Wow!
Oh, I see.
This is totally unrelated to the pliers shop question, but...
Do you tape?
The speed at which you apply it.
Speed?
Was it fast from the beginning?
No, no, no, not at all.
Oh.
Load up the site.
Yes, sir.
I'll take one around there.
Thank you very much.
Yes, sir.
Okay, so here's the protective stuff like this.
Okay.
Okay, what do we do after this?
Let's paint.
Hey!
Yay!
I'm going to paint it!
66DIY
I bought 9 colors to match the members.
Ebichu has an attendance number.
I wanted to paint them in that order.
I would like to paint them in that order.
The first one is
My first one...
I'd like to paint it yellow.
That's great!
Oh, no. Oh, no.
Don't open it.
Oh!
That's great!
Looks smurfy!
I'd like to paint it in a color that matches its height!
Here we go!
Oh, height, this one.
This one, this one, this one, yes!
Wow! Wow!
Oh, wow! It's hard to sew straight!
What a surprise!
This is so much fun!Awesome fun!
Wow, that's great.
It's fun.
I'll just let it mosey along for a bit then.
Mmm-hmm.
Next time
Light blue.
Riko Nakayama
I'd like to paint 161cm.
Okay, then.
That's 168.
Well...
So that's 170 at most.
Uh-huh.
About...
Yes, sir.
Okay.
Heh heh heh.
Oh, that's fun.
I'm gonna let it grow a little bit. Like a cactus.
Wow, this seepage is amazing
Uh, uh, uh, uh
Here
Whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa
What a roller
I feel like I want to paint forever.
It's that much fun.
Mayama-san is the smallest.
Actually, he is not that tall.
Kashiwagi-san is the same height.
Ha-ha-ha!
That's why.
Oh, he's cute.
He's got straight eyes.
Let's read "Wakakusa-san" as "Wakakusa" in Japanese next time.
I'll read "Wakakusa".
A little...
She's a little shabby.
Well, she's finally started to eat properly.
He's been on ebutin for a year now, and he's eating his meals.
I can't keep up my strength.
He was saying that.
Watch out!
You have incredibly long legs.
a little bit... at the waist.
Okay, Ayaka...
You've unexpectedly shrunk in height. I wonder if you've grown... around.
Yes, sir.
That uncle...
He's super stoic.
I'll straighten him out.
It's a little plant-like, but cute.
I don't have room to paint.
It's a little bit...
I got half of it wrong.
I can't really tell.
It's white.
It's just a little blah, blah, blah.
I'm only in ninth grade.
I have a bright future ahead of me.
Ha-ha-ha
Like there are so many choices
A bit like a branch
Like a branch.
Oh, but
I saw Mayama-san yesterday.
He's the most senior person here.
He's the most senior of all of us, but...
This is the last
Mayama Rikapaisen
This is
Tiny.
Tiny
tiny
Tiny!
Shaped a little like a jar
Cute
Yes, sir.
It's OK.
I painted 9 people in order of height.
I'm going to go ahead and paint them.
I'd like to paint them.
I bought some tile stickers, so I'd like to put them on.
byyy byyy byyy byyy byyy byyy byyy byyy byyy byyy byyy byyy byyy byyy
Okay...
Ha-ha-ha-ha!
Last time.
When you made the desk...
And the time you made me a bench.
If you've been watching me...
You might know what I'm talking about.
Okay! Yes!
I wrote Poe!
It's done!
I'm satisfied! I am satisfied!
Log Log DIY!
What is the theme?
It's right on the money!
The height of Minichu!
Hmmm...
I don't know...I don't know.
I feel like a member of this group.
A little adult.
I'm in my third year.
A little mature.
If you make it rounded, it looks mature.
Yasumoto-san...
I feel the life force.
It can be leafy or leafy.
But stoic.
Mini is
Her waist is very high
Her body shape is extremely
Because she has a good style
like from the waist to the feet.
from the waist to the feet.
Hinata has a straight voice.
You have a straight voice.
I tried to make it a bit louder
like a dekunovo, but a little louder.
Nakayama-san's voice is
Nakayama-san's voice is funky or wild.
She's a little bit wild.
a little bit wild.
And Mr. Sakuragi
Her dancing is so beautiful.
She's beautiful, so it's a little bit
I want her to be supple.
And Koka-san grew up on sweets.
so she's a little wide and slender.
Slender.
Lastly, Kazami-san is the best.
She's in her third year.
She's very straight, but...
I wonder what kind of boy he will grow up to be.
I wonder what kind of girl she'll grow up to be.
I'm looking at her from a big sister's point of view.
I want you to have a good future.
I hope you have a good future.
I hope you will have a good future.
In the last issue
benches and tables
I wrote about benches and tables
but it's different from that.
I thought it would be a different theme
I thought it would be a good theme
I went to buy scribble paper
Peel it off
Stick it on
designing it.
It's really careful
I don't know, it's a lot of work.
There are so many parts that I have to pay attention to.
Try it once
I'd like to try it.
I'd like to replace the walls
I'd like to replace the walls in my own house.
It was so much fun!
I think I'll be able to sleep well today.
So, if you enjoyed this video
I hope you like this video.
I hope you like it.
If you don't, please subscribe to my channel immediately.
If you haven't already, please subscribe to our channel
Like and comment!
I'd love it if you'd like to comment.
If you have any other comments, please leave them.
I'd love to hear your other comments.
That's all for now.
Good bye!
Lastly, I'd like to introduce our products.
The new safety shoes are easy to walk in and have less foot sway even when walking.
The upper is a cool graphical design that is hard to slip on water and oil-covered floors.
Excellent grip to prevent slipping even on floors covered with water or oil.
Please check out the overview section!
Please subscribe to our channel!